night games and Airsoft the two mix
together very well and if they're done
right they mix together extremely
well one all the guys with night vision
are all put on one team and everybody
without night vision is put on the other
team it's not fun for anybody the guys
without nods are obviously just getting
shot from bushes they can't see and when
you have a really quiet gun it's just
like why are they even here why did they
pay money and then the guys with night
vision they want to do cool stuff with
their nods and part of doing cool stuff
is actually having some type of threat
from the other side being able to just
sneak up behind them and shoot targets
without really giving yourself away is
not fun it's just not fun I've played a
lot of night games where that was the
case here at Zulu 24 uh they found a
really good balance for running night
games so that guys with nods and Guys
Without nods can all have fun together
uh aside from Team balancing the biggest
thing that balances those night games is
Tracer units nobody's really safe from
detection once they start shooting and
then when you start throwing in Tracer
units that have a muzzle flash it gets
even spicier so if you're a guy with
nods and you just start shooting where
you see somebody and your gun gives you
away all of a sudden you're going to
have a bunch of white lights in your
face and you're not really going to be
able to see them and all of a sudden
you're not as safe as you thought you
were so now all of a sudden a product
like a tracer unit which was something
that I really felt like I didn't need at
all is now a product where I'm kind of
going down the rabbit hole trying to
find which one is going to be really
dope which one's going to be really cool
to use fortun Ely e shooter sent us
their flare M BT Tracer unit to do a
review of and I'm actually really
excited for this I think this is going
to be the Tracer that I use from now on
it has a lot of cool features on it it's
very cool design we're going to talk all
about that before we do that let's get
into the full disclosure like I said e
shooter sent this to me for free there
was no exchange of money uh they've
actually been sending this Tracer unit
along with uh their ecro mosfets out to
other YouTubers to do reviews of so this
is part of their uh uh marketing scheme
and there's nothing wrong with that I'm
going to be as unbiased as I can be
while reviewing this for you guys and I
will also add that they did send me a
eestl V2 basic and an eastel V3 basic to
do a review of and there is going to be
videos for that coming up in the future
so what really stands out about this
Tracer unit from the gecko is that it
does have Bluetooth built into it and
you can program it through an app on
your phone and we're going to show you
screen recordings of me going through
those settings and messing with
stuff also it's a very compact size and
we can talk about the actual build of
the Tracer unit in a little bit I put
this Tracer unit in a category of
tracers that are compact but also have
that function of being able to drop into
a airsoft mock suppressor another neat
feature that really stands out on this
Tracer unit is that it does have a
integrated chronograph which is really
cool I don't think I've ever seen a
tracer unit on the market that's this
small that has a
self-contained
chronograph there are similar products
that go on the muzzle of your airsoft
gun and they will Chrono the gun but
there's usually an external component
that you might Mount to your rail that
will actually tell you what the reading
is but with this one you get the reading
through the app so so let's talk about
the muzzle flash settings really quick
and what you can do with it there's a
couple of preset colors for the muzzle
flash that you can program just by
hitting the buttons on the Tracer unit
you could also go to the app to pick the
same pre-selected colors I had a hard
time choosing which one to use because
I'm color blind I need a Jordan to help
me out with that so aside from the
pre-selected colors on the muzzle flash
you can also adjust the the intensity of
the brightness from a selection from 1
to 10 and you can also add a a dynamic
color mode where it'll switch between
different colors of the rainbow the
actual Tracer unit is just a very bright
UV light like you'd see on any other
Tracer unit as far as programming it you
can turn it off to just have the muzzle
flash or there's a drag mode which
actually illuminates every fourth BB so
it almost simulates having a mixed bag
of tracers but you're you're going to
get more Precision in the space between
your traced shots and your non- Tred
shots often times Tracer units that are
available will either Mount directly to
your muzzle threads or they will insert
into a mock suppressor of some sort and
for something that has so many features
really the fact that it's small the
chronograph blows me away this thing is
super small you can insert it into
pretty much any can now a lot of other
tracers on the market their overall
diameter will be specific to some
specific cans but this Tracer unit is
actually smaller and that's something
that I prefer because what that means is
that you can basically get any type of
spacer you want to fit this into a wider
variety of cans so if it's a really
skinny can you probably will be able to
fit it in there and if it's a larger can
like this Surefire replica that I have
here brought to me by uh Zulu outdoor
it'll fit in there too as long as I use
a spacer for it so I did make a 3D
printed sleeve for this Tracer
specifically to fit in this can
specifically and that might be a product
that anac Airsoft puts out if uh you
know these Tracer units take off and if
certain types of uh mock cans take off
if there's any type of standard I'll
definitely accommodate the player base
as much as I can with that cuz I think
it's really dope to put this inside of a
can another reason why I really favor
the modularity of this Tracer unit to
fit in a wider variety of cans is that
airsofters to this day still use that
old school technique of just sticking a
super long inner barrel in their gun no
matter what it is but the problem is is
if your inner barrel is extending beyond
your muzzle threads and it's going into
your tracery
unit that can it will it'll make it not
work you can't have any obstruction
inside the Tracer unit because you'll be
blocking the sensor that detects the BB
that tells the computer to light up the
UV LED that illuminates your bb so
putting this in a can gives you the
ability to some degree to actually let
your inner barrel stick out a little bit
more but you can offset the position of
the Tracer unit so that it's closer
towards the end of that muzzle device so
here's my replica Shire can it's just a
hollow tube it doesn't do anything it's
not real it's mock all right ATF get
over it so here's the sleeve that I made
for the Tracer unit I did the cad in
like 5 minutes and it took about 45
minutes to print so very neat I did use
some tape to shim it up but that's going
to go right inside my can and then I'm
going to use a spring as a spacer to
finish it off and then we'll be able to
close this up put it on my
M4 and test it so I'm starting off with
this because I want to show you guys
what that muzzle flash looks like from
inside of a can so let's shoot
it so now we have it mounted directly to
the muzzle we're not going to talk in
between each shoot now we're just going
to cycle through the different muzzle
slash colors and settings and you guys
can look at it and when we do the
comparison it'll be the same thing just
shooting you guys can look at it you can
be the judge which one is uh the one you
want to get
oh bro that
looks so testing out the rainbow
settings we figured that maybe uh
there's some function to them that'll
work better on Full Auto so we switched
out the kythera for an AEG so we could
shoot full auto so I'm going to go back
to
one on
rainbow all right all right good
[Applause]
yeah what it's just red it it's just
purple just purple yeah
well there is a dynamic rainbow mode
okay so let's try
that let's try 16 again really quick
yeah
16 it's just right yep my gun can't keep
up with my uh sorry my mag my mags can't
keep up with the gun with Dynamic
rainbow there's a Time wheel where you
can change how many seconds have to pass
in order for the color to change it's
going to cycle through all the preset
colors so we'll set it to 0. five
seconds now it's cool now it's cool now
it's cool that's going to look real cool
on full
off if the mag decides it wants to keep
up all right full auto now
honestly it would wait for semi now
we're going to cycle through the
brightness I'm just going to go from 1
to 10 and then you can use your
imagination to figure anything in
between that
addd
brake we like to do things a little bit
differently here at antec we're going to
do the unboxing now towards the end of
the video because nobody actually cares
about it that much the packaging is
actually quite nice it's more than I was
expecting from a company based where
this company is based
in so you do get a little baggie it
comes with an allen key and an adapter
so you can screw it onto your gbb pistol
you get the manual the manual is going
to go
over pretty much how to set it up how to
use the
app and all that other stuff I did uh
write a bunch of scribble notes in here
while we were filming at night so that I
had some semblance of a
script it does come with the Tracer unit
of course and there's also going to be a
USBC cable I misplaced it with all my
other gear cuz
msome now looking at the unit during the
day you actually see how well it's built
the housing is a nice aluminum
construction and the caps on it are also
aluminum so you have really nice solid
threads on it I don't see this thing
stripping out on you anytime soon there
is an o-ring on the bottom of this cap
to keep water out otherwise the other
end is pretty
watertight and you know you haven't
screwed on all the way cuz all four LEDs
will be exposed in those little windows
on the front
taking another look at the guts of this
thing something stuck out to me that I
thought was actually really nice uh
there are a couple there's two little uh
lithium batteries in here lithium
batteries come and go what's nice is
that these are just kind of plugged in
and taped into place if these batteries
fail you have the exact specs of the
battery right here you could probably go
on Digi key and get a replacement
battery for like a couple of dollars so
that's really nice you're not going to
have to replace the whole unit should it
fail taking the guts out you can see the
port here for the USBC cable you are
going to have to take it out and order
to charge it I don't really have a
problem with that the alternative is
that the USBC cable is always exposed
and now you have this place where water
can get into or dirt and grime and it
it's just I hate when it happens to my
phone and I have to clean out the
charging port every few weeks because of
the dust in my pocket so it's nice that
if Apple can't do it at the very least
shooter thought about that and they have
that Port protected speaking of
Apple the app that they have that works
with this Tracer unit uh along with
their other products you can get it on
iOS or Android which is a big plus it
sucks when you can't get an app on Apple
uh nobody really cares about Apple that
much so to see that there is a company
that does care about Apple so the way
that you use the app is you open it up
you're going to see the list of products
that es shooter sells that this app is
compatible with you're going to go over
to your flare MBT and you're going to
turn on the Tracer unit you do that by
pressing the M button now that the
Tracer unit is on you'll see your device
I named mine antec it will have a
default name that you can
change and just like that it shows your
browsing history and the last four
digits of your Social Security not just
kidding fortunately I don't have to
update the app right the second in order
to use it when your flare is attached to
it it you'll notice on the very top you
have this thing that says 5.56
mm25 G that is not referring to a 5.56
round that's actually referring to the
diameter of the BB and that's so that
you can program this for the built-in
Chrono so you can actually go in there
and you can change your bullet
settings BBS are not always perfectly 6
mm they're usually actually going to be
uh 5.95 mm generally so I'm just going
to set that now because of OCD you can
go to kinetic
and you can actually set a limit so that
when your gun is shooting above a
certain Jewel limit it'll actually give
you a warning just in case you wanted to
respect people's safety you can go into
settings and when you go into the
settings part it's going to open up all
the programming features for the Tracer
M itself so you get to select your modes
between flame flame and Tracer Tracer or
drag light we already went through what
all of these settings do I'm just kind
of showing you what it looks like on the
app so looking at the flame you see that
you have this RGB wheel where you can
kind of spin it around and pick a more
unique color than the provided uh eight
colors on that palette so you can use
the RGB wheel or you could just select
one of the colors on the palette below
and you can also select the brightness
we talked about it before but the
brightness only affects the muzzle flash
it doesn't affect the brightness of the
Tracer itself so you can choose a single
color color you can choose a rainbow or
you can do a dynamic rainbow where the
rainbow actually changes over a course
of time so if you're doing a lot of Full
Auto fire that's something that you'll
really see otherwise if you do the
rainbow uh that color is just going to
change every shot or
so there's a sensor test mode if you
scroll down and you can turn it on and
when you turn it on it basically gives
you two checks if both of your sensors
are working and if you don't get two
checks then that means that there's
something wrong with your sensors tells
you the version that you're on for the
firmware of the
app and you can also set it to speed
measurement only you could exclusively
just use this as a chronograph if you
wanted to do that on the top you can
change the device name we're going to
name it poop just so I can show you how
that works poop now my device is named
Poop it's not a poop product though poop
is just funny my final thoughts what do
I think of this product in my opinion
this is the last Tracer unit that I
probably ever have to buy it does
everything I needed to do and then some
I was a little bit skeptical about the
chronograph at first but after seeing
all the settings and seeing the type of
data that I can collect with that
chronograph this almost turns into a
diagnostic tool that I can use while
teching and I like that a lot like a lot
a lot more than the average Airsoft
viewer probably would think but as a
tech I actually think that this is a
very valuable tool in my collection as
far as the brightness it was bright
enough for me to have a lot of fun and
get the giggles while I was shooting it
the Tracer unit works exactly as it
should work
and just simply put I I really don't
have a need for any other Tracer unit
unless if it produces fog and smoke e-
shooter e- shooter you guys should
totally make cans or inserts like this
that also emit smoke out of the muzzle
because that would be very very based
all right guys so this was a really fun
video to make I do a lot of in the
gearbox type stuff when I do decide to
make content it's nice to do a little uh
switch a Rooney on you and review
something that isn't directly related to
making the gun work uh so big shout out
thank you to e shooter for sending this
over for the review I do hope that my
review gave you guys a good data point a
good preference for you when you're
deciding to go and pick out a tracer
unit guys that's pretty much all I got
uh one more time thank you uh es shooter
for sending this over uh you guys are
going to get your ecal mosfet reviews
done as soon as I can get to putting
them in you know a couple of my own
personal guns uh thank you to Zulu 24
for letting us film this and shoot some
glow-in-the-dark bbb's at night during
off hours the field is not open right
now thank you Zulu outdoor for all the
cool attachments and accessories that
you guys hook me up with on my guns uh
you guys really know where to Source
them and then lastly thank you Jordan
for filming this it's nice that I don't
have to film or edit the video uh I
don't make as much content as I'd like
to because I hate editing it so big
shout out to Jordan espa photos he's uh
he's a great photographer he does all
the film stuff for Zulu so he's really
nice I I hope this video does uh this
product Justice you guys can uh make up
your own mind as to what you want it's
all I got
everyone's going to think off camera I'm
standing here holding it